Contact

32, G 10th Street, Linganaya Palya, Halasuru, Bengaluru 560008. +91 8523944995 (Home) sivaarwin7@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/siva-k (LinkedIn) github.com/sivaarwin (Other) www.energyhelpline.com/ (Company)

Top Skills

MicroStrategy

Amazon Redshift

Apache Superset

Languages

Telugu (Elementary)
English (Full Professional)
Kannada (Limited Working)
Tamil (Native or Bilingual)
German (Elementary)

Certifications

Implementing Data Models and Reports with Microsoft SQL Server Introduction to Programming Using Python

Querying Microsoft SQL Server 2012/2014

Python for Data Science and Al Development

SQL Fundamentals

Honors-Awards

IOT WORKSHOP CAMPUS AMBASSADOR

Employee of the Month Employee of the Month

Siva Krishnamurthi

Data Operator at Zepto | Product Analytics | Microstrategy BI | Superset | Data Analyst

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Data Analyst who is interested in interpreting and analyzing data in order to drive successful business solutions. Proficient Knowledge of ML algorithms, Statistics, Mathematics, and Analytics. Excellent Understanding of Business operations and analytical tools like MS Excel, Python, Tableau, Amazon Redshift(SQL), Apache Superset, and Microstrategy BI for effective analysis of data. Experience in Text Mining(web scraping) Text classification using Python + Selenium Webdriver, and cooked several dishes like NER - Name Entity Recognition(NLP) to get accurate customer details.

Experience

Zepto

Data Operator

October 2022 - Present (8 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

working closely with the Product, Product Analytics and Product Ops team in: Fetching and harmonising the data from multiple sources (online + offline) to drive efficient product roll outs

Build and manage dashboards in Microstrategy, Excel and superset to see trends and patterns as per requirement

Flipkart

Management Information System Executive July 2021 - October 2022 (1 year 4 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Work closely with stake holders/ senior management to support strategic planning, reporting activities by providing actionable assessments of daily, weekly and monthly reports like IBL issues, recall reports, RBND, DBNS & ABNR, expectancy changes of orders, shipments pendency reports and service under conditions reports with existing and potential in the areas of data analysis, blessed with certain responsibilities like collecting and manipulating the data in order to achieve business goals on daily basis.

SaveBySwitching Global Solutions Pvt Ltd. 1 year 8 months

Senior Tariff Analyst May 2021 - July 2021 (3 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Executive - Tariff Analyst December 2019 - May 2021 (1 year 6 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Experience in Handling multiple Pricing Data Sheet, Supplier Emails, and cross-functional Tasks

Blessed with responsibilities like Top 20 tariffs reporting, Text Mining, Data Preparation, KPI trackers, and ROTA experience in manipulating data from multiple DB and other sensitive Data.

INNODATATICS * Innovation | Data | Analytics
Data Science Intern
June 2019 - December 2019 (7 months)
Bengaluru Area, India

Worked as a data science Intern in a warranty claim project - we need to make an analysis on a dataset which contains consumer details and few other information which will be used to predict the percentage and number of fraudulent claims occured in a multi-brand showroom across India.

Education

Anna University Chennai

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2015 - 2019)

Seventh Day Adventist Higher Secondary School Primary to Higher Secondary schooling (2000 - 2015)